<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Dónde Va</string>
    <string name="authenticate">Authenticate</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm password</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign in</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign up</string>
    <string name="sign_up_description">Don\'t have an account? Click here to create one</string>
    <string name="account_already_created">Already have an account? Click here to sign in</string>
    <string name="sign_out">Log out</string>
    <string name="sign_out_title">Log out?</string>
    <string name="sign_out_description">You\'ll have to sign in again to see your notes</string>
    <string name="delete_account">Delete account</string>
    <string name="delete_account_title">Delete account?</string>
    <string name="delete_account_description">You\'ll lose all your notes and your account will be deleted. This action cannot be undone.</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="analyze">Analyze</string>
    <string name="cardboard">Cardboard</string>
    <string name="glass">Glass</string>
    <string name="metal">Metal</string>
    <string name="paper">Paper</string>
    <string name="plastic">Plastic</string>
    <string name="miscellaneous">Miscellaneous</string>
    <string name="see_details">See details</string>
    <string name="dismiss">Dismiss</string>
    <string name="analyze_image">Analyze image</string>
    <string name="analyzing">Analyzing</string>
    <string name="signing_in">Signing in</string>
    <string name="signing_up">Signing up</string>
    <string name="fill_all_fields">Fill all fields</string>
    <string name="incorrect_credentials">Incorrect credentials</string>
    <string name="passwords_do_not_match">Passwords do not match</string>
    <string name="account_already_exists">Account already exists</string>
    <string name="password_must_be_at_least_six_characters_long">Password must be at least 6 characters long</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="scanned">Scanned</string>
    <string name="analyze_another_object">Analyze another object</string>
    <string name="loading_item">Loading item</string>
    <string name="cardboard_information"># Can I recycle pizza boxes?\n\nYes! Pizza boxes can be recycled, even if they have grease in them. Make sure to remove any food scraps from the box and flatten it before placing it in the bin.\n\n# Are paper and cardboard takeout containers recyclable?\n\nIt depends on how much food is left on them. Try rinsing or scraping the residue off to clean it. “Spatula-clean” is clean enough to recycle! Otherwise, containers contaminated with food cannot be recycled.\n\n# Can cardboard containers and boxes be recycled?\n\nYes, make sure to flatten any boxes before placing them in the bin. Examples of recyclable cardboard containers are some egg cartons, cereal boxes, and shoe boxes.\n\n# Can gift wrap be recycled?\n\nPaper gift wrap often is not recyclable when it has a shiny or laminated coating. If you use gift wrap, purchase a type that can be recycled or is made from recycled content. EPA encourages consumers to reuse gift bags, boxes, and tissue paper. Newspaper is an excellent alternative to gift wrap.</string>
    <string name="glass_information">Glass, especially glass food and beverage containers, can be recycled over and over again. In the United States [in 2018](https://www.epa.gov/facts-and-figures-about-materials-waste-and-recycling/national-overview-facts-and-figures-materials), 12.3 million tons of glass were generated, 31.3 percent of which was recycled. Making new glass from recycled glass is typically cheaper than using raw materials. \n\n# Can I recycle different glass colors/types together?\n\nMost curbside recycling programs accept different glass colors and types mixed together and then sort the glass at the recovery facility. \n\n# Can I recycle broken glass?\n\nNo, broken glass should not go into the recycling bin. Glass shards can harm workers and damage equipment. \n\n# Can I leave my metal bottle cap on my glass bottle when I recycle?\n\nNo, metal bottle caps should be recycled separately from the glass bottles.</string>
    <string name="metal_information">[In 2018](https://www.epa.gov/facts-and-figures-about-materials-waste-and-recycling/national-overview-facts-and-figures-materials), 19.2 million tons of ferrous metals (iron and steel) were generated. EPA estimates that the recycling rate of ferrous metals from durable goods was 27.8 percent. The same year, 2.5 million tons of nonferrous metals (not containing iron) were generated. The recycling rate for nonferrous metals was approximately 68 percent.\n\n# How do I recycle metal?\n\nThere are different programs and options for metal recycling depending on your locality. Check to find out what is available in your area.\n\n# Aluminum\n\n[In 2018](https://www.epa.gov/facts-and-figures-about-materials-waste-and-recycling/national-overview-facts-and-figures-materials), 3.9 million tons of aluminum municipal solid waste was generated. The total recycling rate for aluminum items was 34.9 percent. Both aluminum cans and foil can be recycled. \n\n## Should aluminum cans be crushed before recycling them?\n\nNo, generally, aluminum cans should not be crushed before they are recycled. For areas with single-stream recycling, crushed cans are harder to detect when being sorted at recycling facilities. If you live in an area with multi-stream recycling, crushing cans is not an issue. \n\n## Can I recycle aluminum foil?\n\nYes, aluminum foil can be recycled. Make sure to remove any food residue before recycling.</string>
    <string name="paper_information">Paper makes up 23 percent of municipal solid waste (trash) generated each year, more than any other material. Americans recycled about 68 percent of the paper they used [in 2018](https://www.epa.gov/facts-and-figures-about-materials-waste-and-recycling/paper-and-paperboard-material-specific-data). This recovered paper is used to make new paper products, which saves trees and other natural resources. Most community or office recycling programs accept paper and paper products. Check what your community or office program accepts before you put it in the bin. Look for products that are made from recycled paper when you shop. Better yet, consider if you really need to print in the first place.\n\n# Can I recycle newspapers?\n\nYes, newspapers can be recycled. \n\n# Can I recycle magazines?\n\nYes, magazines can be recycled. \n\n# Can I recycle mail?\n\nYes! Even envelopes with plastic windows can be recycled.\n\n# Are paper and cardboard takeout containers recyclable?\n\nIt depends on how much food is left on them. Try rinsing or scraping the residue off to clean it. “Spatula-clean” is clean enough to recycle! Otherwise, containers contaminated with food cannot be recycled. \n\n# Can shredded paper be recycled?\n\nIt depends on your local recycling program. \n\n# Can books be recycled?\n\nIf the book is still in good condition, try donating it! Schools, places of faith, charities, and non-profits will often accept book donations. If the book is not in usable condition, it can be recycled. Paperback books can be recycled as-is; remove the cover from a hardcover book before recycling it.\n\n# Can gift wrap be recycled?\n\nPaper gift wrap often is not recyclable when it has a shiny or laminated coating. If you use gift wrap, purchase a type that can be recycled or is made from recycled content. EPA encourages consumers to reuse gift bags, boxes, and tissue paper. Newspaper is an excellent alternative to gift wrap.</string>
    <string name="plastic_information">More than 35 million tons of plastics were generated in the United States in 2018 and only 8.7 percent was recycled. Some types of plastics are not accepted in community recycling programs. Check with your local recycling program to find out which types of plastic they accept. When possible, purchase products made from recycled plastic materials. \n\n# Can I recycle plastic bags, wraps and films?\n\nThese items are recyclable, but they cannot go in your household recycling bin. Retail and grocery stores often accept these materials for recycling. If necessary, be sure to cut off the sealable zippers from sandwich bags before recycling them. Please ask your local grocery and department store, or visit the [Earth911](https://earth911.com/) to find a location near you that recycles plastic bags and plastic wrap/film. \n\n# Can plastic bottles and caps be recycled?\n\nYes, typically the caps and labels can be left on the bottles as well.\n\n# Can polystyrene foam (styrofoam) be recycled?\n\nVery few localities accept styrofoam in curbside recycling. Check [Earth911](https://earth911.com/) to learn where you can drop off your styrofoam for it to be recycled.\n\n# Can plastic containers, cups and utensils be recycled?\n\nIt depends on what types of plastic the containers and cups are made of and whether your local program accepts them. Items with food debris cannot be recycled. Plastic utensils also cannot be recycled. \n\n# Can I recycle compostable or bio-based plastics?\n\n*Compostable Plastic*: No. Compostable plastics are not intended for recycling and can contaminate and disrupt the recycling stream if mixed with non-compostable plastics. If your community does not have a composting recycling pick-up program that accepts compostable plastic, contact your garbage/recycling company or local government to find out if there are any drop-off locations for your compostable plastic items.\n\n*Biobased Plastics*: To determine what waste disposal options are available for a biobased plastic item, it is necessary to read the product’s label as to its compostability and recyclability. \n\nLearn more by reading the [Frequently Asked Questions about Plastic Recycling and Composting](https://www.epa.gov/trash-free-waters/frequently-asked-questions-about-plastic-recycling-and-composting#diff). \n\n# What do the symbols mean on the bottom of plastic bottles and containers?\n\nThese symbols were created to identify the type of plastic used to make the container. This can help you determine whether the item is recyclable by your local program. The resin number is contained in a triangle that looks very similar to the recycling symbol. However, this symbol does not necessarily mean it can be collected for recycling in your community.\n\n# Can I recycle plastic containers that had food in them?\n\nIt depends on how much food in on the containers and what type of plastic containers your local recycling program accepts. First, check with your local recycling program for what plastics they accept (refer to the question above about resin codes to help you with this!). Then, if accepted by your local recycling program, rinse or scrape any food residue off to clean the containers. “Spatula-clean” is clean enough to recycle!</string>
    <string name="miscellaneous_information"># What should I do with dirty diapers?\n\nWhile we provide general guidance below, please check with your local solid waste agency or recycling program first.\n\nGenerally, you should flush the excrement down the toilet, and then place the diaper in the trash. Consider using reusable cloth diapers instead of disposable diapers.\n\n# What should I do with old clothes and old shoes?\n\nGently worn clothes and shoes can be donated to many charities. For damaged clothes and shoes, please double-check with your local charity to determine if it will accept them. Some retail stores recycle clothing or shoes. Check your local ones to find out if they accept these items for recycling.</string>
    <string name="more_information_about_recyclables">**Learn more:**\n\n[Governmental Agreement 164-2021](https://www.marn.gob.gt/reglamento-164-2021/)\n\n[How do I recycle common recyclables](https://www.epa.gov/recycle/how-do-i-recycle-common-recyclables)</string>
    <string name="google_logo_description">Google logo</string>
    <string name="no_accounts_error">No Google accounts found on this device</string>
    <string name="unexpected_credential">Unexpected type of credential</string>
    <string name="get_credential_error">Error getting credential</string>
    <string name="sign_in_with_google">Sign in with Google</string>
    <string name="sign_up_with_google">Sign up with Google</string>
    <string name="or">or</string>
</resources>